<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>net.corluma.Corluma</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LicenseRef-proprietary</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <url type="homepage">https://corluma.net</url>
  <name>Corluma</name>
  <summary>Control Philip's Hues, LIFX, Nanoleafs, and Arduinos.</summary>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <description>
    <p>
      Corluma provides users with multiple color pickers and palettes to quickly choose the exact right color for your lights. For lights that support it, Corluma can also create and access lighting routines that change colors over time. Do you have too many lights? Simplify managing them by grouping them and controlling them all at once. Did you spend a lot of time getting your lights to look <i>just</i> right? You can save light settings and set them back to their exact state at a later date with just a few clicks.
    </p>
    <p>
	This app does not require an account, external servers, or additional permissions such as location data. All communication is done on local wifi. You no longer have to worry about losing the ability to turn off your lights if the internet goes down.
    </p>
    <p>
	For Arduinos, Corluma is compatible with the ArduCor sketch which is compatible with NeoPixels, Rainbowduinos, and standard LEDs. For nanoleafs, Corluma is compatible with all lights <i>except</i> the Nanoleaf Essentials line. 
    </p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/timsee/Corluma-flathub/main/screenshots/color_page.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/timsee/Corluma-flathub/main/screenshots/lights_page.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/timsee/Corluma-flathub/main/screenshots/palette_page.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/timsee/Corluma-flathub/main/screenshots/routines_page.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
     <release version="0.37.20" date="2023-08-11">
      <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Added support for grouping lights by location (IE, Home, Beach House, Work).</li>
            <li>Added better support for light firmware effects, such as the "Candle" and "Fire" effects on newer Hues.</li>
            <li>Fixed miscellaneous bugs.</li>
          </ul>
      </description>
     </release>
     <release version="0.36.05" date="2023-07-01">
      <description>
          <ul>
            <li>Fixed UI bugs when handling multiple Hue Bridges.</li>
            <li>Added more information to LIFX discovery widgets.</li>
            <li>Fixed miscellaneous bugs.</li>
          </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.35.14" date="2023-06-18"/>
  </releases>
  <url type="homepage">https://corluma.net</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://corluma.net/contact</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.corluma.Corluma.desktop</launchable>
</component>

